Guide to the Alex Harris photographs and papers, 1970-2015 RL.10060
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- River of Traps, 1978-1980; 9; 2 boxes; 30 prints
  - Jacobo Romero telling stories, El Valle, New Mexico, 1979 April (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0302)
  - Jacobo Romero, El Valle, New Mexico, 1979 June (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0303)
  - Jacobo in Eloisa's garden, El Valle, New Mexico, 1979 August (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0304)
  - Jacobo Romero, El Valle, New Mexico, 1979 June (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0305)
  - Bialquín Pacheco, Vallecito, New Mexico, 1979 November (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0317)
  - Tranquilino and José Aguilar, El Valle, New Mexico, 1979 November (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0319)
  - Bialquín Pacheco, Vallecito, New Mexico, 1980 February (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0320)
  - Telling stories, Las Trampas, New Mexico, 1979 June (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0327)
  - Jacobo Romero (82nd birthday portrait), El Valle, New Mexico, 1979 June 11 (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0328)
  - Jacobo in the forest at Rito de la Olla, New Mexico, 1979 September (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0329)
  - Jacobo Romero at his barn, El Valle, New Mexico, 1979 August (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0330)
  - Jacobo in his barn, 1979 July (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0331)
  - Jacobo Romero after the flood, El Valle, New Mexico, 1979 September (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0332)
  - Jacobo's hay, El Valle, New Mexico, 1979 August (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0333)
- Rainbow Gathering, 1979 July; 10; 2 boxes; 11 prints
  While in New Mexico in 1979, Harris traveled to the nearby Rainbow Gathering, an annual counter-culture festival and encampment. There, he photographed men, women, and children, many of them nude, as they danced, built fires, told stories, bathed, and played instruments. The 11 gelatin silver images measure 11x14 (9) and 16x20 inches (2), and were printed in 1999-2000. Titles assigned by photographer.
  - Snake woman, Rainbow Gathering, Alpine, Arizona, 1979 July (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0306)
  - Putting out a fire, Rainbow Gathering, Alpine, Arizona, 1979 July (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0307)
  - Rainbow Gathering, Alpine, Arizona, 1979 July (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0308)
  - Bathing, Rainbow Gathering, Alpine, Arizona, 1979 July (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0309)
  - Mud man, Rainbow Gathering, Alpine, Arizona, 1979 July (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0310)
  - Mud man and three girls, Rainbow Gathering, Alpine, Arizona, 1979 July (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0311)
  - Rainbow Gathering, Alpine, Arizona, 1979 July (Box 17, Print RL10060-P-0312)
  - Rainbow Gathering, Alpine, Arizona, 1979 July (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0336)
  - Rainbow Gathering, Alpine, Arizona, 1979 July (Box 19, Print RL10060-P-0337)
- Philadelphia Experience Corps, 1999 May; 11; 4 boxes; 56 prints
  These black-and-white images were taken by Harris in May 1999 as part of an assignment to document interactions between volunteer reading tutors over the age of 55 and elementary school students in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. The Experience Corps is currently sponsored by the U.S. organization AARP. Most of the subjects, including volunteers, are African American. Gelatin silver prints measure 11x14 inches. Harris continued this work until 2005, with many later images taken in color. A selection of images was exhibited in the U.S. Senate Russell Building Rotunda in July 2005. Titles assigned by photographer.
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0338)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0339)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0340)
  - Washington School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0341)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0342)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0343)
  - Taylor School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0344)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0345)
  - Locke School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0346)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0347)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0348)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0349)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0350)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 20, Print RL10060-P-0351)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0352)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0353)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0354)
  - Taylor School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0355)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0356)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0357)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0358)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0359)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0360)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0361)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0362)
  - Washington School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0363)
  - Washington School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0364)
  - Washington School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 21, Print RL10060-P-0365)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0366)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0367)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0368)
  - Locke School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0369)
  - Locke School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0370)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0371)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0372)
  - Locke School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0373)
  - Locke School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0374)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0375)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0376)
  - Locke School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0377)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0378)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 22, Print RL10060-P-0379)
  - Locke School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0380)
  - Locke School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0381)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0382)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0383)
  - McClure School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0384)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0385)
  - Taylor School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0386)
  - Taylor School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0387)
  - Taylor School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0388)
  - Locke School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0389)
  - Morrison School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0390)
  - Rowen School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0391)
  - Taylor School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 1999 (Box 23, Print RL10060-P-0392)
- Old And On Their Own, 1990-1992; 12; 3 boxes; 21 prints
  21 gelatin silver prints of African American and white older people living on their own in the central North Carolina Piedmont communities of Durham, Cedar Grove, and other places. This commissioned project provided documentary images for a study by Robert Coles, also published in book form as Old and On Their Own (1997). Prints measure 11 x 14 inches and are matted. Printed in 1992. Titles assigned by photographer.
  - Roy Tapp, 86 years old, retired sharecropper, farmer, Cedar Grove, North Carolina, 1992 May (Box 24, Print RL10060-P-0393)
  - Dwight Billings, 79 years old, retired botany professor, Durham, North Carolina, 1990 August (Box 24, Print RL10060-P-0394)
  - Augusta Brimage Turner, 76 years old, retired public relations director, rehabilitation counselor, Raleigh, North Carolina, 1992 April (Box 24, Print RL10060-P-0395)
  - Henry Markham, 81 years old, farmer, Durham, North Carolina, 1990 June (Box 24, Print RL10060-P-0396)
  - Raymond Corn, 75 years old, retired boxer and contractor, Durham, North Carolina, 1992 January (Box 24, Print RL10060-P-0397)
  - Lillie Vanhoook Beasley, 82 years old, retired sharecropper, Cedar Grove, North Carolina, 1992 June (Box 24, Print RL10060-P-0398)
  - Villa Zala, 86 years old, writer, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, 1992 April (Box 24, Print RL10060-P-0399)
  - Edith London, 81 years old, painter, Durham, North Carolina, 1990 July (Box 25, Print RL10060-P-0400)
  - William Evans, 67 years old, retired sharecropper, Durham, North Carolina, 1990 June (Box 25, Print RL10060-P-0401)
  - Claude Carmelia, 82 years old, retired army sergeant, Durham, North Carolina, 1992 June (Box 25, Print RL10060-P-0402)
  - Gilbert Fountain, 86 years old, retired scrapyard worker, salvager, Durham, North Carolina, 1990 June (Box 25, Print RL10060-P-0403)
  - Charlotte Earth Adams, 90 years old, mediator, 1992 April (Box 25, Print RL10060-P-0404)
  - Bayard Hedrick, 76 years old, retired government worker, artist, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, 1992 June (Box 25, Print RL10060-P-0405)
  - Lorenzo Beasley, 76 years old, rettired sharecropper and custodian, Cedar Grove, North Carolina, 1992 May (Box 25, Print RL10060-P-0406)
  - John "Shag" Stewart, 82 years old, retired bank president, Durham, North Carolina, 1992 May (Box 76, Print RL10060-P-0407)
  - Doctor Ralph Beasley, 84 years old, retired farmer, Hurdle Mills, North Carolina, 1992 May (Box 76, Print RL10060-P-0408)
  - Clara Sims, 90 years old, retired hospital worker, Durham, North Carolina, 1990 August (Box 76, Print RL10060-P-0409)
  - Glenn Pursselley, 76 years old, retired Air Force Sergeant, P.O.W., Durham, North Carolina, 1992 April (Box 76, Print RL10060-P-0410)
  - Edward Nell Toole, 92 years old, electrician, Durham, North Carolina, 1990 September (Box 76, Print RL10060-P-0411)
  - Herbert Andrews, 93 years old, tailor, Durham, North Carolina, 1990 August (Box 76, Print RL10060-P-0412)
  - Martha Branscombe, 84 years old, retired child relief worker, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, 1992 May (Box 76, Print RL10060-P-0413)
- Mobile, Alabama, 2009-2010; 13; 3 boxes; 138 prints
  Due to the vulnerability of very large digital prints, a full set of smaller viewing copies is available for research access.
  Contains 69 large (24x36 inch) pigmented color inkjet photographs taken by Alex Harris in Mobile, Alabama for a documentary book project co-authored with naturalist Edward O. Wilson, whose childhood was spent in this area of the South. The book is entitled Why We Are Here: Mobile and the Spirit of a Southern City (2012). The prints were part of an exhibit in the Mobile Museum of Art from October 2012-January 2013.
  Images include portraits of Mobile citizens from various backgrounds; a football team's practices and prayer circles; women's church groups; Civil War re-enactors; street scenes; Mardi Gras events, including balls and receptions; and landscapes, including images of the Gulf of Mexico and of local and state parklands. Includes a portrait of naturalist E.O. Wilson, kneeling down to look at ants. Titles assigned by photographer.
  The 69 prints measure 24x30 inches and were made on an Epson 7900 stylus pro, using Epson ultrachrome hdr inks.
  The large format prints are closed to general use. A full set of 69 11x17 inch viewing copies, also pigmented color inkjet prints, are available in a separate box.
  - Murphy High School Panthers with coach Ronn Lee, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 October 11 (Box 62, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0414)
  - Mobile Delta, Alabama, 2009 October 6 (Box 62, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0415)
  - Duckblind cane, osprey nest on dead cypress, Mobile Delta, Alabama, 2009 October 6 (Box 62, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0416)
  - Ben Davis, Cedar Point Pier, Mobile, Alabama, 2009 October 7 (Box 62, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0417)
  - Dale Turner, on the Crescent Towing tug "Noon Wednesday," Mobile River and Cochrane–Africatown USA Bridge, Mobile, Alabama, 2009 October 7 (Box 62, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0418)
  - Major General Gary Cooper, Mobile, Alabama, 2009 October 9 (Box 62, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0419)
  - Willie Brown, dry kiln supervisor at Scotch & Gulf Lumber LLC, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 October 7 (Box 62, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0420)
  - UMS Wright football practice, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 October 12 (Box 62, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0421)
  - Murphy High School marching band, before the Murphy-Citronelle game, Ladd Peebles Stadium, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 October 14 (Box 62, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0422)
  - Lewis Island, Chuckfee Bay, Mobile Delta, Alabama, 2009 October 7 (Box 62, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0423)
  - Murphy Panther prayer, half-time, Murphy-Citronelle game, Ladd Peebles Stadium, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 October 14 (Box 62, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0424)
  - Robert Hunter, Spring Hill, Mobile, Alabama, 2009 October 9 (Box 62, Folder 3, Print RL10060-P-0425)
  - UMS Wright Bulldogs, entering Cooper Stadium for second half against the Thomasville Tigers, 2010 October 8 (Box 62, Folder 3, Print RL10060-P-0426)
  - Cole Brothers Circus, Mobile, 2010 October 10 (Box 62, Folder 3, Print RL10060-P-0427)
  - Bill Finch, Dyas Creek Swamp, Baldwin County, Alabama, 2010 April 13 (Box 62, Folder 3, Print RL10060-P-0428)
  - Modern dance class, Murphy High, 2010 October 14 (Box 62, Folder 3, Print RL10060-P-0429)
  - Margaret Langdon Hamilton in her Mardi Gras gown, Mobile, Alabama, 2009 October 2 (Box 62, Folder 4, Print RL10060-P-0430)
  - Mobile Bay at Fairhope, Alabama, 2009 October 2 (Box 62, Folder 4, Print RL10060-P-0431)
  - Antonio Holmes, Christian Robinson, Thomas Haring, and Conner McClerry (l-r), holding a rat snake at Five Rivers State Park, Alabama, 2009 October 3 (Box 62, Folder 4, Print RL10060-P-0432)
  - Ken McGhee, Beetle Bailey, and Stephen Ellison, Magee Farm, Kushla, Alabama, 2009 October 4 (Box 62, Folder 4, Print RL10060-P-0433)
  - Kudzu and artificial palm tree, Mobile, Alabama, 2009 October 8 (Box 62, Folder 4, Print RL10060-P-0434)
  - Bellingrath Gardens gift shop, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 April 12 (Box 62, Folder 5, Print RL10060-P-0435)
  - Rosa Barahona, Mobile, 2010 April 8 (Box 62, Folder 5, Print RL10060-P-0436)
  - Murphy High School Panthers, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 October 11 (Box 62, Folder 5, Print RL10060-P-0437)
  - UMS Wright Bulldogs, football practice, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 October 12 (Box 62, Folder 5, Print RL10060-P-0438)
  - Modern dance class, Murphy High, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 October 14 (Box 62, Folder 5, Print RL10060-P-0439)
  - Lenora Ash's House, Fairhope, Alabama, 2010 April 8 (Box 62, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0440)
  - Bass Pro Outdoor World, Spanish Fort, Alabama, 2009 October 7 (Box 62, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0441)
  - Murphy High School trophy room and auxiliary library, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 October 10 (Box 62, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0442)
  - Boy Scouts from troops 28, 292, and 600, Five Rivers State Park, Alabama, 2009 October 3 (Box 62, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0443)
  - Kyle Tucker, Captain for Crescent Towing on the tugboat, "Noon Wednesday," Mobile harbor, Alabama, 2009 October 7 (Box 62, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0444)
  - Grand Marshall's Reception, Battle House Renaissance Hotel, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 12 (Box 63, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0445)
  - Martin Lanaux, Knoll Park, Fairhope, Alabama, 2010 February 12 (Box 63, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0446)
  - Mardi Gras Parade, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February (Box 63, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0447)
  - Word of Life Church, South Atmore Avenue, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 13 (Box 63, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0448)
  - Mistresses of Joe Cain, Mardi Gras, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 14 (Box 63, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0449)
  - Japonica camellia, Auburn Cooperative Extension Service, Fairhope, Alabama, 2010 April 7 (Box 63, Folder 1, Print RL10060-P-0450)
  - Atamasco lilies, mud swamp at Hal's Lake near Carlton, Alabama, 2010 April 11 (Box 63, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0451)
  - Stewart Memorial Christian Methodist Church, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 14 (Box 63, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0452)
  - Indian Mound State Park, Dauphin Island, Alabama, 2010 April 8 (Box 63, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0453)
  - Indian Mound State Park, Dauphin Island, Alabama, 2010 July 8 (Box 63, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0454)
  - Word of Life Church, South Atmore Avenue, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 13 (Box 63, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0455)
  - Drawing cards for next morning's turkey hunting territories, Choctaw Bluff Hunting Club, Alabama, 2010 April 10 (Box 63, Folder 2, Print RL10060-P-0456)
  - Star and Marty Stapleton's pier, Dauphin Island, Alabama, 2010 April 8 (Box 63, Folder 3, Print RL10060-P-0457)
  - Loblolly Pine Nursery, Semmes, Alabama, 2010 July 9 (Box 63, Folder 3, Print RL10060-P-0458)
  - Wrestlers Taylor James (l) and Jacob Vandee. Background: Sandy Stimpson; foreground: Dan Elcan. Choctaw Bluff Hunting Club, Alabama, 2010 April 10 (Box 63, Folder 3, Print RL10060-P-0459)
  - Oliver "Bully" Jackson at his childhood home, Choctaw Bluff, Alabama, 2010 April (Box 63, Folder 3, Print RL10060-P-0460)
  - Choctaw Bluff Hunting Club, Alabama, 2010 April 10 (Box 63, Folder 3, Print RL10060-P-0461)
  - Grand Marshall's Ball, Battlehouse Hotel, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 12 (Box 63, Folder 4, Print RL10060-P-0462)
  - Periwinkle snails on cord grass, Grand Bay marsh, Alabama, 2010 July 12 (Box 63, Folder 4, Print RL10060-P-0463)
  - Captain Brent (Hollywood) and Pam Shaver, Orange Beach, Alabama, 2010 July 13 (Box 63, Folder 4, Print RL10060-P-0464)
  - Sasagu and Junko Yoda, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 July 16 (Box 63, Folder 4, Print RL10060-P-0465)
  - Eastern tiger swallowtail and pitcher plants, Splinter Hill Bog, Alabama, 2010 July 19 (Box 63, Folder 5, Print RL10060-P-0466)
  - E.O. Wilson Looking at Ants, Fort Morgan Ferry, Gulf Shores, Alabama, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 5, Print RL10060-P-0467)
  - Football Practice, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 5, Print RL10060-P-0468)
  - Fairhope, Alabama, 2010 February 11 (Box 63, Folder 5, Print RL10060-P-0469)
  - Longleaf pines, Knoll Park, Fairhope, Alabama, 2010 February 12 (Box 63, Folder 5, Print RL10060-P-0470)
  - Birthday girls, Stewart Memorial Christian Methodist Church, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 14 (Box 63, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0471)
  - Truat V. Nguyen and his goddaughter, Brittany, South Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 7 (Box 63, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0472)
  - Order of Butterfly Maidens Parade, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 6 (Box 63, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0473)
  - Terrilynn and Mike Benintende, Mardi Gras camp, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 7 (Box 63, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0474)
  - Mardo Gras Nacho Stand, American Legion yard, Government Street, Mobile, 2010 October 8 (Box 63, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0475)
  - Hoji (Buddhist Memorial service for the deceased), Mrs. Heak Hong's home, Irvington, Alabama, 2010 February 9 (Box 63, Folder 6, Print RL10060-P-0476)
  - Mobile Warriors High School Band, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February (Box 63, Folder 7, Print RL10060-P-0477)
  - Davidson High School band members Kelante Buskey and Clifford Atchison, before the Order of LaShe Parade, Mobile, Alabama, 2010 February 9 (Box 63, Folder 7, Print RL10060-P-0478)
  - Lenora Ash's House, Fairhope, Alabama, 2010 April 8 (Box 63, Folder 7, Print RL10060-P-0479)
  - Roy Hyde, Fairhope, Alabama, 2010 February 10 (Box 63, Folder 7, Print RL10060-P-0480)
  - Roy Hyde, Fairhope, Alabama, 2010 February 10 (Box 63, Folder 7, Print RL10060-P-0481)
  - Prescribed Burn, Longleaf Pines, Mobile Botanical Gardens, 2010 February 11 (Box 63, Folder 7, Print RL10060-P-0482)
  - Viewing prints for Mobile, Alabama series, 11x17 inches, 1 box; 69 prints (Box 64)
- Dream of a House, 2011; 61 prints 2 boxes
  The series contains 61 17x24 inch color inkjet prints of interior views of the former home of author Reynolds Price, a friend of the photographer, taken in 2011 after Price's death. There are also 61 jpeg files of the images, and a print essay by Harris. Images include views of rooms with numerous artworks and closeups of individual art pieces in Price's house. The photographs were published in Dream of a House (2017). Titles assigned by photographer.
  Artist's abstract: "My wife Margaret Sartor and I were friends with Reynolds Price as well as his relatively close neighbors. Over the years, we visited Reynolds many times in his home on Cornwallis Road in Durham. We marveled as his collections grew, particularly after he was confined to a wheelchair in 1984 until his death in 2011. That spring of 2011, I was asked to document Reynolds' home before it was dismantled. Initially I made these photographs as a collection for the Archive of Documentary Arts to accompany the Reynolds Price Archive at Rubenstein. But after making the pictures, along with Margaret I began to see connections between the man, his writing, and the collections in his home."
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  The photographs are pigmented inkjet images, printed in 2017 on Canson Infinity Platine Fibre Rag (without optical brighteners), using an Epson Stylus Pro 7900 printer and Epson Ultrachrome HDR Ink.
  - Reynolds Price's home, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0495)
    Original digital file ID:
    DSC_4059-a
  - The top of a dresser in Reynolds Price's home, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0496)
    DSC_4404
  - Detail from a portrait of Reynolds Price, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0497)
    DSC_3818
  - Reynolds Price's living room #1, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0498)
    DSC_3729-2
  - Reynolds Price's living room #2, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0499)
    DSC_3765
  - Reynolds Price's bathroom, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0500)
    DSC_4388
  - Reynolds Price's dining area, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0501)
    DSC_4045
  - Reynolds Price's office #1, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0502)
    DSC_4072
  - Reynolds Price's living room #3, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0503)
    DSC_3984
  - Reynolds Price's office #2, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0504)
    DSC_4004
  - Reynolds Price's pantry door, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0505)
    DSC_4277
  - Reynolds Price's dining area #2, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0506)
    DSC_4545
  - Reynolds Price's exercise/gallery room, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0507)
    DSC_4362
  - Reynolds Price's kitchen, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0508)
    DSC_3643
  - Reynolds Price's kitchen and dining area, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0509)
    DSC_3989
  - Reynolds Price's entryway and stairway to the upstairs, 2011 (Box 77, Print RL.10060-P-0510)